ALES Records 5225
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Northwest conference, "Food, people, and industrial potential," Minneapolis, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Northwest conference, "Food, people, and industrial potential," Minneapolis, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Northwest conference, "Food, people, and industrial potential," Minneapolis, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Northwest conference, "Food, people, and industrial potential," Minneapolis, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 18)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 19)
- Farmer-labor conference, North Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 20)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 21)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 22)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 23)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 24)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 25)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 26)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 27)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 28)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 29)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 30)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 31)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 32)
- Farmer-Labor conference, South Dakota, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 33)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 34)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 35)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 36)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 37)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 38)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 39)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 40)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 41)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 42)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 43)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 44)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 45)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 46)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 47)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 48)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 49)
- International project, Minneapolis, Minn., 1955-1958 (Box 73, Folder 50)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 51)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 52)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 53)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 54)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 55)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 56)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 57)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 58)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 59)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 60)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 61)
- Duluth, Minn., World Affairs Conference, "Labor's stake in world affairs", 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 62)
- CIO/ALES, Seminar of World Affairs, Des Moines, Iowa, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- CIO/ALES, Seminar of World Affairs, Des Moines, Iowa, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- CIO/ALES, Seminar of World Affairs, Des Moines, Iowa, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- CIO/ALES, Seminar of World Affairs, Des Moines, Iowa, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- CIO/ALES, Seminar of World Affairs, Des Moines, Iowa, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- CIO/ALES, Seminar of World Affairs, Des Moines, Iowa, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- CIO Seminar on World Affairs, 1956 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- CIO Seminar on World Affairs, 1956 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- ILO Meeting, Des Moines, Iowa (Box 74, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Iowa Federation of Labor (Box 74, Folder 10)
- LeHigh Valley Education Council, Penn (Box 74, Folder 11)
- UN study tour by United Steel Workers, Local 2323, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Penn group, UN study tour, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Textile workers UN study tour, 1956 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Colorado UN seminary correspondence, 1953-1958 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Colorado UN seminary correspondence, 1953-1958 (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Colorado UN seminary correspondence, 1953-1958 (Box 74, Folder 17)
- Colorado UN seminary correspondence, 1953-1958 (Box 74, Folder 18)
- Colorado UN seminary correspondence, 1953-1958 (Box 74, Folder 19)
- Colorado UN seminary correspondence, 1953-1958 (Box 74, Folder 20)
- New England conference, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 21)
- New England conference, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 22)
- UN weekend for American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFC&ME), Massachusetts, 1954- 1955 (Box 74, Folder 23)
- UN weekend for American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFC&ME), Massachusetts, 1954- 1955 (Box 74, Folder 24)
- UN weekend for American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFC&ME), Massachusetts, 1954- 1955 (Box 74, Folder 25)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology Employees Union, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 26)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology Employees Union, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 27)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology Employees Union, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 28)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology Employees Union, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 29)
- AFC&ME, New England regional conference on world affairs (Box 74, Folder 30)
- AFC&ME, New England regional conference on world affairs (Box 74, Folder 31)
- AFC&ME, New England regional conference on world affairs (Box 74, Folder 32)
- International Association of Machinists, ALES conference on World Affairs, Seattle (Box 74, Folder 33)
- International Association of Machinists, ALES conference on World Affairs, Seattle (Box 74, Folder 34)
- International Association of Machinists, ALES conference on World Affairs, Seattle (Box 74, Folder 35)
- International Association of Machinists, ALES conference on World Affairs, Seattle (Box 74, Folder 36)
- International Association of Machinists, ALES conference on World Affairs, Seattle (Box 74, Folder 37)
- International Association of Machinists, ALES conference on World Affairs, Seattle (Box 74, Folder 38)
- International Association of Machinists, ALES conference on World Affairs, Seattle (Box 74, Folder 39)
- International Association of Machinists, ALES conference on World Affairs, Seattle (Box 74, Folder 40)
- Berkeley conference on World Affairs, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 41)
- Berkeley conference on World Affairs, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 42)
- Berkeley conference on World Affairs, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 43)
- United Automobile Workers women's conference on Atomic hazards, Berkeley, 1957 (Box 74, Folder 44)
- United Automobile Workers women's conference on Atomic hazards, Berkeley, 1957 (Box 74, Folder 45)
- White Collar conference, Berkeley, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 46)
- California World Affairs project, 1957-1959 (Box 74, Folder 47)
- California World Affairs project, 1957-1959 (Box 74, Folder 48)
- California World Affairs project, 1957-1959 (Box 74, Folder 49)
- California, Consumer conferences, 1958-1959 (Box 74, Folder 50)
- Texas "Labor's responsibility in International Affairs", 1956 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  co-sponsored by ALES and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union
- Texas "Labor's responsibility in International Affairs", 1956 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Texas "Labor's responsibility in International Affairs", 1956 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Texas "Labor's responsibility in International Affairs", 1956 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Texas "Labor's responsibility in International Affairs", 1956 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Texas "Labor's responsibility in International Affairs", 1956 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Texas "Labor's responsibility in International Affairs", 1956 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Texas "Labor's responsibility in International Affairs", 1956 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Atomic Energy Seminar, New York City, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Atomic Energy Seminar, New York City, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Atomic Energy Seminar, New York City, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- ALES, International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers Institute conference on automation, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- ALES, International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers Institute conference on automation, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 13)
- Teachers' Institute, Rockford, Ill. (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 17)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 18)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 19)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 20)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 21)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 22)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 23)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 24)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 25)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 26)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 27)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 28)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 29)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 30)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 31)
- Canadian Labour Congress, UN study tour, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 32)
- Consumer project, 1958 (Box 75, Folder 33)
- Consumer project, 1958 (Box 75, Folder 34)
- Women's conference for women union members in New York and New Jersey on "Your Job and Foreign Trade", 1959 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Women's conference for women union members in New York and New Jersey on "Your Job and Foreign Trade", 1959 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Women's conference for women union members in New York and New Jersey on "Your Job and Foreign Trade", 1959 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Women's conference for women union members in New York and New Jersey on "Your Job and Foreign Trade", 1959 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Women's conference for women union members in New York and New Jersey on "Your Job and Foreign Trade", 1959 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Women's conference for women union members in New York and New Jersey on "Your Job and Foreign Trade", 1959 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Women's seminar, "World Issues in an Election Year", 1960 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Women's seminar, "World Issues in an Election Year", 1960 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Women's seminar, "World Issues in an Election Year", 1960 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Women's seminar, "World Issues in an Election Year", 1960 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Women's seminar, "World Issues in an Election Year", 1960 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Women's seminar, "World Issues in an Election Year", 1960 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- Women's seminar, "World Issues in an Election Year", 1960 (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Women's seminar, "World Issues in an Election Year", 1960 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- Women's seminar, "World Issues in an Election Year", 1960 (Box 76, Folder 15)
- Women's Seminar, "Women and Human Rights", 1961 (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Women's Seminar, "Women and Human Rights", 1961 (Box 76, Folder 17)
- Women's Seminar, "Women and Human Rights", 1961 (Box 76, Folder 18)
- Women's Seminar, "Women and Human Rights", 1961 (Box 76, Folder 19)
- Women's Seminar, "Women and Human Rights", 1961 (Box 76, Folder 20)
- Women's Seminar, "Women and Human Rights", 1961 (Box 76, Folder 21)
- Women's Seminar, "Women and Human Rights", 1961 (Box 76, Folder 22)
- Women's Seminar, "Women and Human Rights", 1961 (Box 76, Folder 23)
- Women's Seminar, "Women and Human Rights", 1961 (Box 76, Folder 24)
- ALES, International Federation of Free Journalists conference on "Labor Press and the UN", 1959 (Box 76, Folder 25)
- ALES, International Federation of Free Journalists conference on "Labor Press and the UN", 1959 (Box 76, Folder 26)
- ALES, International Federation of Free Journalists conference on "Labor Press and the UN", 1959 (Box 76, Folder 27)
- ALES, Greater Cincinnati Labor Education conferences, 1958-1961 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- ALES, Greater Cincinnati Labor Education conferences, 1958-1961 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- ALES, Greater Cincinnati Labor Education conferences, 1958-1961 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- ALES, Greater Cincinnati Labor Education conferences, 1958-1961 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- ALES, Greater Cincinnati Labor Education conferences, 1958-1961 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- ALES, Greater Cincinnati Labor Education conferences, 1958-1961 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO, ALES Summer School, "Labor's Stake in World Affairs," Columbus, Ohio, 1957-1958 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO, ALES Summer School, "Labor's Stake in World Affairs," Columbus, Ohio, 1957-1958 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO, ALES Summer School, "Labor's Stake in World Affairs," Columbus, Ohio, 1957-1958 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- ALES, International Association of Machinists, conference, "Labor and World Issues," Cleveland, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- ALES, International Association of Machinists, conference, "Labor and World Issues," Cleveland, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- ALES, International Association of Machinists, conference, "Labor and World Issues," Cleveland, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- ALES, International Association of Machinists, conference, "Labor and World Issues," Cleveland, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- ALES, International Association of Machinists, conference, "Labor and World Issues," Cleveland, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- ALES, International Association of Machinists, conference, "Labor and World Issues," Cleveland, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- ALES, International Association of Machinists, conference, "Labor and World Issues," Cleveland, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- ALES, International Association of Machinists, conference, "Labor and World Issues," Cleveland, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 17)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 18)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 19)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 20)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 21)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 22)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 23)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 24)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 25)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 26)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 27)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 28)
- ALES, Ohio Federation of Labor conference on atomic energy, Cleveland, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO and Railroad Brotherhood Unions in Cleveland, conference on automation, Cleveland, 1957 (Box 77, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO and Railroad Brotherhood Unions in Cleveland, conference on automation, Cleveland, 1957 (Box 77, Folder 31)
- AFL-CIO and Railroad Brotherhood Unions in Cleveland, conference on automation, Cleveland, 1957 (Box 77, Folder 32)
- AFL-CIO and Railroad Brotherhood Unions in Cleveland, conference on automation, Cleveland, 1957 (Box 77, Folder 33)
- AFL-CIO and Railroad Brotherhood Unions in Cleveland, conference on automation, Cleveland, 1957 (Box 77, Folder 34)
- Conference on economic progress, Cleveland, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 35)
- Conference on economic progress, Cleveland, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 36)
- Conference on economic progress, Cleveland, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 37)
- Conference on economic progress, Cleveland, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 38)
- Conference on economic progress, Cleveland, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 39)
- Conference on economic progress, Cleveland, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 40)
- Cleveland conference, "Productivity, prices, peace", 1959 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Cleveland conference, "Productivity, prices, peace", 1959 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Cleveland conference, "Productivity, prices, peace", 1959 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Cleveland conference, "Productivity, prices, peace", 1959 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Cleveland conference, "Productivity, prices, peace", 1959 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Cleveland conference, "Productivity, prices, peace", 1959 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Cleveland conference, "Productivity, prices, peace", 1959 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Cleveland conference on aging, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Cleveland conference on aging, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Cleveland conference on aging, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Cleveland conference on aging, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Cleveland conference on aging, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Cleveland conference on aging, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Cleveland conference on aging, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Cleveland conference on health, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Cleveland conference on health, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Cleveland conference on health, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Cleveland conference on health, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 18)
- Cleveland conference on health, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Cleveland conference on health, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 20)
- Cleveland group, UN study tour, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 21)
- Delaware County community project, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 22)
- Delaware County community project, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 23)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  includes urban development, conference on Christians and Jews, women's conference, consumer projects, retirement, public speaking: correspondence with community leaders such as Barry Bingham, Editor, The Louisville Times, and others.
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 25)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 26)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 27)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 28)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 29)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 30)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 31)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 32)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 33)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 34)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 35)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 36)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 37)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 38)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 39)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 40)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 41)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 42)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 43)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 44)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 45)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 46)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 47)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 48)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 49)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 50)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 51)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 52)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 53)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 54)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 55)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 56)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 57)
- Louisville, Ky. joint AFL-CIO, ALES community project on labor education, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 58)
- Louisville, Ky., community project, 1958-1961 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Louisville, Ky., community project, 1958-1961 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Louisville, Ky., community project, 1958-1961 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Louisville, Ky., community project, 1958-1961 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Louisville, Ky., community project, 1958-1961 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Louisville, Ky., community project, 1958-1961 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Louisville, Ky., community project, 1958-1961 (Box 79, Folder 7)